export const QuizData = [
{  
  Category : "JavaScriptData",
  data : [
    {
      question: "Q:1 I'm very happy _____ in India. I really miss being there.",
      Options: ['to live', 'to have lived', 'to be lived', 'to be living'],
      correct: 'to live',
      userselect: '',
      id: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Q:2 They didn't reach an agreement ______ their differences.",
      Options: ['on account of', 'due', 'because', 'owing'],
      correct: 'due',
      userselect: '',
      id: 2
    },
    {
      question: "Q:3 I wish I _____ those words. But now it's too late",
      Options: [
        'not having said',
        'have never said',
        'never said',
        'had never said',
      ],
      correct: 'not having said',
      userselect: '',
      id: 3
    },
    {
      question: 'Q:4 The woman, who has been missing for 10 days, is believed _____.',
      Options: [
        'to be abducted',
        'to be abducting',
        'to have been abducted',
        'to have been abducting',

      ],
      correct: 'to have been abducted',
      userselect: '',
      id: 4
    },
    {
      question: 'Q:5 She was working on her computer with her baby next to _____.',
      Options: ['herself', 'her', 'her own', 'hers'],
      correct: 'her',
      userselect: '',
      id: 5
    },
    {
      question: 'Q:6 _____ to offend anyone, she said both cakes were equally good.',
      Options: [
        'Not wanting',
        'As not wanting',
        "She didn't want",
        'Because not wanting',
      ],
      correct: 'Because not wanting',
      userselect: '',
      id: 6
    },
    {
      question: "Q:7 _____ in trying to solve this problem. It's clearly unsolvable.",
      Options: [
        "There's no point",
        "It's no point",
        "There isn't point",
        "It is no need",

      ],
      correct: 'It is no need',
      userselect: '',
      id: 7

    },
    {
      question: 'Q:8 Last year, when I last met her, she told me she _____ a letter every day for the last two months.',
      Options: ['had written', 'has written', 'had been writing', 'wrote'],
      correct: 'had written',
      userselect: '',
      id: 8
    },
  ]
},  

   
{  
  Category : "ReactNativeData",
  data : [
    {
      question: "Q:1 What is React Native?",
      Options: ['JavaScript library', 'JavaScript framework', 'Programming language', 'Neither of the above'],
      correct: 'JavaScript library',
      userselect: '',
      id: 1
    },
    {
      question: "Q:2 React Native has a set components for:",
      Options: ['IOS platform', 'Android platform', 'Both IOS and Android platform', 'None'],
      correct: 'Both IOS and Android platform',
      userselect: '',
      id: 2
    },
    {
      question: "Q:3 JSX stands for",
      Options: [
        'JavaScreenXML',
        'JointScript XML',
        'none',
        'JavaScript XML',
      ],
      correct: 'JavaScript XML',
      userselect: '',
      id: 3
    },
    {
      question: 'Q:4 Select apps which used react native .',
      Options: [
        'Airbnb',
        'pinterest',
        'All',
        'Instagram',

      ],
      correct: 'All',
      userselect: '',
      id: 4
    },
    {
      question: 'Q:5 Which statement is true for props?',
      Options: ['it is mutual', 'it is set and updated by the object', 'can be modified', 'can’t be modified'],
      correct: 'can’t be modified',
      userselect: '',
      id: 5


    },
    {
      question: 'Q:6 ________is used to create immutable stylesheet references',
      Options: [
        'none',
        'Redux',
        "Interaction manager",
        'stylesheet',


      ],
      correct: 'stylesheet',
      userselect: '',
      id: 6
    },
    {
      question: "Q:7 To update react native with latest version what will you use?",
      Options: [
        "both",
        "react-native init",
        "react-native upgrade",
        "none",

      ],
      correct: 'react-native upgrade',
      userselect: '',
      id: 7

    },
    {
      question: 'Q:8 React native was initially released in',
      Options: ['2000', '2015', '2014', '2008'],
      correct: '2015',
      userselect: '',
      id: 8
    },
  ]
}, 

]


